Guide to the Terry Sanford Papers, 1926-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Legislative Files Series, 1986-1992
  - Foreign Relations Subseries, 1986-1992
    - Defense, 1986-1992
      - Army Research Office: RTP, 1988-1991 (Box 99)
      - ATF-23, 1990 (Box 99)
      - Ayala, Eddie and Jerry Eliott, 1988 (Box 99)
      - Barnes, Mike, 1991 (Box 99)
      - Base closure, 1991 (Box 99)
      - Blacks in the military/guard/reserve, 1990-1991 (Box 99)
      - Chemical weapons, 1990 (Box 99)
      - Cola-Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
      - Combat Boot/McCrae-Welko, 1987-1991 (Box 99)
      - Conventional Armed Forces in Europe Treaty, 1991 (Box 99)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 99)
      - Correspondence, 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 100)
      - Co-Sponsors, 19901-991 (Box 100)
      - CREE (Cree Research, Inc.), 1991-1992 (Box 100)
      - Cummins (Cummins Military Systems Company: SLEP (Service Live Extension Program), 1992 (Box 100)
      - Dear Colleague, 1987-1989, (3 folders) (Box 100)
      - Defense authorization, 1991 (Box 100)
      - Defense Logistics Agency, 1988 (Box 100)
      - Department of Defense Appropriations, 1987-1992, (10 folders) (Box 100)
      - Department of Defense Appropriations, 1989-1992, (19 folders) (Box 101)
      - Department of Defense Appropriations, 1992 (Box 102)
      - Department of Defense participation at historically Black colleges and universities/minority institutions, 1990 (Box 102)
      - Dukakis defense materials, 1988 (Box 102)
      - Empress II, 1988 (Box 102)
      - F-15, 1992 (Box 102)
      - F-15: Sea Wolf (Box 102)
      - Family Support Services, 1991 (Box 102)
      - Fast food/military bases:
        - 1987-1988 (Box 102)
        - Bojangles: Richardson, Billy, 1988-1989 (Box 102)
      - Fort Bragg:
        - Land acquisition, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 102)
        - Mental health project: Behar, Lenore, 1985-1987, (3 folders) (Box 102)
        - Visit: Codel, 1991, Feb. (Box 102)
      - FSX Fighter Agreement with Japan, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 102)
      - Gays in the military, 1992 (Box 102)
      - Ground Wave Emergency Network (GWEN), 1990 (Box 102)
      - Historical fact sheet, 1992 (Box 102)
      - INF, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 102)
      - Information security, 1985-1988 (Box 102)
      - Invitations, 1989 (Box 102)
      - Jet Research Center, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 102)
      - Johnson, Samuel, undated (Box 103)
      - Korean War Veterans, 1992 (Box 103)
      - Korean War Veterans Memorial, 1990 (Box 103)
      - Lindsay, James (USA General Ret.), 1988-1992 (Box 103)
      - LTV Corporation: Possible foreign buyout, 1992 (Box 103)
      - Madey, John, 1989-1990 (Box 103)
      - Marine Corps Air Museum, 1988-1990 (Box 103)
      - Memos to Terry Sanford, 1990 (Box 103)
      - Memorandum, 1987-1992 (Box 103)
      - Michelin Aircraft Tires, 1992 (Box 103)
      - Middle East Institute, 1989 (Box 103)
      - Mil Con, 1992 (Box 103)
      - Military wives, 1989 (Box 103)
      - Miller, Russell F., 1990 (Box 103)
      - Mills Manufacturing Corp., 1989 (Box 103)
      - Nambia, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - NASA: Edwards, William, 1988 (Box 103)
      - National Archives: World War II: Commemorative Committee, 1990 (Box 103)
      - National Guard:
        - 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 103)
        - Bill, 1989 (Box 103)
        - Letter to Secretary Cheney, 1992 (Box 103)
        - North Carolina, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 103)
      - North Carolina Press and Op. Ed, 1990-1991 (Box 103)
      - Old Messages, 1989-1990 (Box 103)
      - Onslow County: Odom, Claude, 1989-1990 (Box 103)
      - Operations Desert Shield, 1990 (Box 103)
      - Persian Gulf, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - Persian Gulf War, 1990-1991, (4 folders) (Box 103)
      - Persian Gulf War: (Box 104)
        - 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 104)
        - ATandT fax services: Wolf, Diana, 1991 (Box 104)
        - Kuwaiti refugees, 1991 (Box 104)
        - Schwarzkopf war quotes, 1990 (Box 104)
        - Iraq:
          - Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 104)
          - Statements, 1990 (Box 104)
        - Postwar, 1991 (Box 104)
        - Task Force
          - 1991, undated (Box 104)
          - Clippings, 1991 (Box 104)
      - POW/MIA, 1987-1991, (4 folders) (Box 104)
      - PRIMUS/Fort Bragg, 1987-1988 (Box 104)
      - Probe Researcher and USN Destroyer DD997 incident, 1989 (Box 104)
      - Pro-formance: Smith, Clyde, 1990 (Box 104)
      - Reibold, Kay: Vietnam Assistance, 1990-1992, undated (Box 104)
      - Retired Enlisted Association, 1985-1987 (Box 104)
      - ROTC: UNC-Wilmington, 1990 (Box 104)
      - S.533 and S.2292, 1988 (Box 104)
      - S.1381: Veterans, 1991 (Box 104)
      - Saudi Arabia: Arms sales, 1987 (Box 104)
      - Sinclair, David B., 1990 (Box 104)
      - Source Management Co., 1987-1988 (Box 104)
      - Soviet Union, 1987-1992 (Box 104)
      - Space station, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Special Forces Move: GAD, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Special projects, 1987 (Box 104)
      - START (Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty):
        - 1992, (5 folders) (Box 104)
        - Opposition, 1992 (Box 104)
      - START/CFE, 1990 (Box 104)
      - State Militia: Thorpe, Bo, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 105)
      - Statements by Cheney and Powell, 1990 (Box 105)
      - Stewart, Harry E., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Tower, John: Nomination, 1989 (Box 105)
      - Transcontinental Enterprises, Inc., 1988, (2 folders) (Box 105)
      - U.N. Association, 1990 (Box 105)
      - U.N. resolutions, 1990 (Box 105)
      - USS Raleigh:
        - 1991 (Box 105)
        - Julie Wright, 1989 (Box 105)
      - V-22, 1989-1992 (Box 105)
      - VA hospitals:
        - AIDS policy, 1987 (Box 105)
      - VA (Veterans Administration):
        - Hospital prosthesis, 1992 (Box 105)
        - Rural Health Care Initiative, 1992 (Box 105)
        - Smoking, 1992 (Box 105)
      - Veteran's Cemeteries, 1986-1987 (Box 105)
      - Veterans of W.W.I, 1990 (Box 105)
      - Veterans pensions for remarried spouses, 1991 (Box 105)
      - Vietnam legislation, 1992 (Box 105)
      - Vote summaries, 1991 (Box 105)
      - Weapons: START/nuclear and chemical proliferation, 1992 (Box 105)
      - Womack Army Medical Center: Fort Bragg, 1986-1990 (Box 105)
      - Women in combat, 1991 (Box 105)
      - Women in Military Service Memorial, 1991-1992 (Box 105)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-1992, (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - Budget Subseries, 1986-1992
      Correspondence, clippings, staff memoranda, press statements, reports, testimonies, proposals, and other materials pertaining to the formulation of the federal budget. Subjects covered include Social Security, Head Start, drug programs, arts funding, proposed balanced budget constitutional amendments, and efforts to reform the budget process.
      - General/Federal, 1988-1992, (8 folders) (Box 106)
      - Amendments (101st Congress, 1st Session-102nd Congress, 2nd Session), 1988-1992 (Box 106)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1988 (Box 106)
      - Balanced budget (S.101) letters, 1992 (Box 106)
      - Bills (100th Congress, 1st Session-102nd Congress, 2nd Session), 1988-1992 (Box 106)
      - Book: How Real Is the Federal Deficit?, 1986 (Box 106)
      - Budget Resolution Markup, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 106)
      - Budget and debt bills, 1988 (Box 106)
      - Budget summit, 1990 (Box 106)
      - CEO letter, 1989, Mar.3 (Box 106)
      - Chapter 1, 1988-1991 (Box 106)
      - Charts and tables, 1988-1989 (Box 106)
      - Chiles budget resolution, 1987 (Box 106)
      - Committee hearing: Charlotte, N.C., 1989, Nov.6 (Box 106)
      - Conference, 1989 (Box 106)
      - Congressional record, 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 106)
      - Constitutional amendment, 1992 (Box 106)
      - Correspondence: (Box 107)
        - 1987-1992, (4 folders) (Box 107)
        - Budget reform comments to Charlotte Chamber, 1992 (Box 107)
        - Debt Ceiling Amendment Legislation, 1990, July (Box 107)
        - Federal Government Streamlining Act, 1992 (Box 107)
        - North Bill, 1992 (Box 107)
      - Darman letter, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Dear Colleague:
        - Amendment No. 1069, 1989, Oct.27 (Box 107)
        - Extension of Debt Limit, 1987, July21 (Box 107)
        - Request for Floor Speaker, 1990, Oct.10 (Box 107)
        - S.101 as amendment to debt limit legislation, 1990, Oct.2 (Box 107)
        - Democratic Caucus materials, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Drug policy, 1988-1989 (Box 107)
      - Drugs:
        - 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 107)
        - Bennett, William: Hearing, 1990 (Box 107)
        - Biden: Drug Bill, 1990 (Box 107)
        - Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 107)
        - Dear Colleague, 1989-1990 (Box 107)
        - Greensboro hearing, 1989-1990 (Box 107)
      - Early Childhood Education Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 107)
      - Economic Recovery Plan, 1992 (Box 107)
      - Editorials, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Education Summit, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Education services for emotionally disturbed children, 1990 (Box 107)
      - Farm Credit Institutions, 1988-1989 (Box 107)
      - Floor statements, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 107)
      - Floor statements, 1990-1992(2 folders (Box 108)
      - Fort Raleigh, 1990-1991 (Box 108)
      - Greensboro, N.C., 1992 (Box 108)
      - GAO (General Accounting Office), 1989-1990 (Box 108)
      - Government Affairs and Budget Committees Hearing: The Honest Budget, 1989, Oct.6 (Box 108)
      - Head Start, 1986-1990, (4 folders) (Box 108)
      - Head Start and Chapter 1, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - Head Start and education clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 108)
      - Head Start information kit, 1989-1990 (Box 108)
      - Hearing:
        - 1989, Nov. (Box 108)
        - FY 1988Budget Outlook, 1987, Jan.27 (Box 108)
        - Impact of the Deficit and the National Debt on the Business Community, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 108)
        - Letters, 1989 (Box 108)
        - U.S. Competitive Edge: N.C., 1987, Mar.20 (Box 108)
      - Higher Education Colloquium on Science Facilities, 1991 (Box 108)
      - Honest/Balanced Budget Acts, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 108)
      - HUGO/FEMA, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - Labor: Health and Human Services and Education Departments, 1991 (Box 109)
      - Luxury Tax: Boats, 1991 (Box 109)
      - Lyng testimony, 1987, Jan.31 (Box 109)
      - Members of committee, undated (Box 109)
      - Memoranda, 1987-1988 (Box 109)
      - Miscellaneous statements, 1987-1988 (Box 109)
      - National Economic:
        - Commission members, 1988 (Box 109)
        - Commission testimonies, 1988 (Box 109)
        - Recovery Act, 1992 (Box 109)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1991 (Box 109)
      - National Taxpayer's Union (NTU), 1990-1991 (Box 109)
      - New York Times luncheon, 1988, July20 (Box 109)
      - Oregon Inlet, 1991 (Box 109)
      - Poverty, 1992 (Box 109)
      - Press clippings, 1989-1992 (Box 109)
      - Press releases, 1986-1992 (Box 109)
      - Reform:
        - 1988-1989 (Box 109)
        - Comments, 1988-1989 (Box 109)
        - Proposals, 1988-1989 (Box 109)
      - RTC funding/Budget markup, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 109)
      - S. Con. Res. 29: Concurrent Resolution, 1992 (Box 109)
      - S. Con. Res. 30, 1989, May4 (Box 109)
      - S.101, 1991 (Box 109)
      - Sanford- Helms Smokies letters, 1988-1989 (Box 109)
      - Science funding, 1991 (Box 109)
      - Social Security:
        - Information, 1990, Jan. (Box 109)
        - Speech draft by Kevin Sullivan, DPC, 1990 (Box 109)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Arts, 1989 (Box 109)
      - Strauss Commission members, 1988 (Box 109)
      - Streamling Bill (1992), 1992 (Box 109)
      - Tax bill, 1988 (Box 109)
      - Turn back, 1992 (Box 109)
      - Wilderness areas (land acquisition), 1991 (Box 109)
  - Select Committee on Ethics, 1980-1992(bulk 1987-1992)
    Correspondence, reports, and documentation from this committee, which Sanford chaired.
    - 1988-1991 (Box 109)
    - Common Cause, 1990-1991 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 109)
    - D'Amato, 1991 (Box 109)
    - Durenberger hearings, 1990, June (Box 109)
    - Ethics material, 1991 (Box 109)
    - Ethics project file, 1991, June3 (Box 109)
    - Election Commission, 1988 (Box 109)
    - Investigation into SandL Debacle, 1990-1991 (Box 109)
    - Investigations of Senators, 1990-1992 (Box 109)
    - Keating chronology of key contacts, 1990 (Box 109)
    - Keating 5 Press, 1990 (Box 109)
    - Legislative Branch Appropriations Act of 1991, 1992 (Box 110)
    - Opening statement, 1990 (Box 110)
    - Press, 1990 (Box 110)
    - Pro Bono legal representation, 1980-1988 (Box 110)
    - Report of Receipts and Disbursements, 1989 (Box 110)
    - Senator Riegle, 1990 (Box 110)
    - SandL miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
    - Senate Public Financial Disclosure Report, 1989 (Box 110)
    - Rep. James C. Wright, Jr., 1989 (Box 110)
  - Environment Subseries, 1958-1992(bulk 1986-1992)
    Correspondence, staff memoranda, clippings, reports, project plans, impact studies, and other background information. Correspondence includes lobbying material from various industries, environmental organizations, and constituents. Issues addressed include the Clean Air Act, rivers and wetlands, solid, radioactive, and nuclear waste management, forestry, energy resources and policy, North Carolina parks and wilderness legislation, and the Exxon Valdez Oil Spill in Alaska.
    - Agency correspondence, 1991-1992, (5 folders) (Box 111)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), 1989-1990 (Box 111)
    - Alaska oil spill:
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 111)
      - Legislation, 1988-1989 (Box 111)
    - Animal issues, 1987-1989 (Box 111)
    - Animal rights, 1987-1989, (4 folders) (Box 111)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1985-1989 (Box 111)
    - Appropriations:
      - Department of Interior, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - Fiscal year, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box 112)
    - BioMass, Ethanol, Methanol, 1987-1990 (Box 112)
    - Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 112)
    - Choah Bald tree spikes, 1991 (Box 112)
    - Clean Air Act:
      - 1987-1992, (7 folders) (Box 112)
      - Acid rain, 1990(2 folders (Box 112)
      - Acid rain, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Air toxins, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Attainment, 1989-1990, (4 folders) (Box 113)
      - Auto pollution control, warranty extension, 1982-1989 (Box 113)
      - Greenhouse effect, 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Mobile sources, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 113)
      - Ozone layer depletion, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 114)
      - Permits/Enforcement, 1989-1990 (Box 114)
      - Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 114)
      - Toxics, 1989-1990, (5 folders) (Box 114)
    - Clean Air implement, 1990-1991 (Box 114)
    - Clean Water Act, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 114)
    - Coal, 1987-1990 (Box 114)
    - Coastal issues: Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 114)
    - Coastal management, 1992 (Box 115)
    - Coastal: U.S. Army Corps of Engineers project, 1991-1992 (Box 115)
    - Congratulations letters, 1992 (Box 115)
    - Constituent projects, 1986-1990 (Box 115)
    - Cooperative Institute for Fisheries Oceanography: Pivers Island, 1991-1992 (Box 115)
    - Corolla Horses, 1989-1990, undated, (3 folders) (Box 115)
    - Corporate Average Fuel Economy, 1991 (Box 115)
    - Corps, 1992 (Box 115)
    - Co-sponsorship memos, 1991-1992 (Box 115)
    - Cullasja River, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Dairy Bill, 1991 (Box 115)
    - Department of Energy, 1987-1990 (Box 115)
    - Department of Interior, 1989 (Box 115)
    - Disaster Assistance, 1991-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Electric loops, 1992 (Box 115)
    - Electric power, 1987-1990 (Box 115)
    - Electric utilities, 1991-1992 (Box 115)
    - Endangered species, 1991-1992 (Box 115)
    - Energy, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Energy and water, 1989-1991 (Box 115)
    - Energy Bill, 1991 (Box 115)
    - Energy Bill: Requests and thank you's, 1991 (Box 116)
    - Energy efficiency, 1987-1990 (Box 116)
    - Energy ideas, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 116)
    - Energy policy: Efficiency and Renewables, 1986-1990 (Box 116)
    - Energy strategy:
      - 1992 (Box 116)
      - S.1220: Johnston- Wallop Bill: National Energy Security Act, 1991 (Box 116)
      - S.2166: National Energy Security Act, (2 folders) (Box 116)
    - Environment, 1991-1992 (Box 116)
    - Environment Policy: Commentary, 1989-1992 (Box 116)
    - Environment project:
      - Community, 1992 (Box 116)
      - International, 1992 (Box 116)
    - Environmental Protection Agency: Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 116)
    - Environmentally sensitive regions, 1989 (Box 116)
    - Erosion, 1992 (Box 116)
    - Ethanol, 1991-1992 (Box 116)
    - Fish and wildlife, 1986-1988 (Box 116)
    - Fisheries, 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 116)
    - Fisheries, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 117)
    - Food industry: Environmental Protection Agency, 1991 (Box 117)
    - Forestry: (Box 117)
      - 1987-1990 (Box 117)
      - Issues, 1989-1990 (Box 117)
      - Pisgah-Nantahala plans, 1988-1990 (Box 117)
      - Vegetarian management, 1986-1989 (Box 117)
    - Forests, 1987-1990 (Box 117)
    - Forest Road program, 1990 (Box 117)
    - Forest service, 1987-1989 (Box 117)
    - Fort Raleigh, 1991-1992 (Box 117)
    - Fuel efficiency, 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 117)
    - General correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 117)
    - Global warming, 1990-1992 (Box 117)
    - Global House effect, 1991 (Box 117)
    - Gypsy moth, 1991-1992 (Box 117)
    - Hazardous waste: Thermal KEM, 1992 (Box 117)
    - Hazel Creek Bridge, 1989-1991 (Box 117)
    - Henderson, N.C.: GE plant, 1989-1991 (Box 117)
    - Highlands of Roan, 1987-1990 (Box 117)
    - Historic places, 1990-1992 (Box 117)
    - Hunters, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - Hunters, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Hydrilla weed control at Lake Gaston, 1991-1992 (Box 118)
    - Hydropower, 1987-1990 (Box 118)
    - Interior Appropriations: Timber Amendment, 1992 (Box 118)
    - King, Makerel, 1988 (Box 118)
    - Koppers Superfund Site, Morrisville, N.C., 1992 (Box 118)
    - Lake Gaston, 1992 (Box 118)
    - Lake Gaston pipeline, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Land appropriations: Fiscal year, 1993 (Box 118)
    - Lead battery, 1992 (Box 118)
    - Low level radioactive waste, 1986-1990, (3 folders) (Box 118)
    - Marine Mammal Protection Act, 1987-1990 (Box 118)
    - Marine research, 1992 (Box 118)
    - Marine Wildlife Conservation, 1989-1992 (Box 118)
    - McClees, Joe: Fisheries, 1991 (Box 118)
    - Minerals management, 1992 (Box 118)
    - Mobil, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Mobil, 19902 folders) (Box 119)
    - Mobil Drilling, 1991-1992 (Box 119)
    - Mobil Oil, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - Monitored retrievable storage, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - Morehead City Harbor, 1992 (Box 119)
    - Nags Head Woods, 1991 (Box 119)
    - National Coastal Resources Research and Development Institute (NCRI), 1991-1992 (Box 119)
    - National Institute for the Environment, 1991-1992 (Box 119)
    - National Marine Fisheries Service, 1992 (Box 119)
    - National Park Service, 1984-1990 (Box 119)
    - National Wildlife Refuges, 1987-1990 (Box 119)
    - Natural gas, 1987-1989 (Box 119)
    - North Carolina:
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 119)
      - Environment/Law, 1991 (Box 119)
      - Fisheries Association, 1991-1992 (Box 119)
    - Nuclear plans, 1992 (Box 119)
    - Nuclear power:
      - 1986-1990 (Box 119)
      - Emergency planning, 1987 (Box 119)
    - Nuclear waste, 1986-1989 (Box 119)
    - Nuclear waste: (Box 120)
      - 1986-1992, (4 folders) (Box 120)
      - Dumping, 1986-1990 (Box 120)
      - Department of Energy, 1986 (Box 120)
      - Legislation, 1987-1990, (4 folders) (Box 120)
      - North Carolina, 1992 (Box 120)
      - Policy, 1986-1990 (Box 120)
    - OCS (Outer Continental Shelf), 1990-1991 (Box 120)
    - Ocean dumping, 1987-1989 (Box 120)
    - Offshore oil exploration, 1992 (Box 120)
    - Oil and energy, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - Oil spills, 1988-1990 (Box 120)
    - Oregon Inlet, 1965-1990 (Box 120)
    - Oregon Inlet, 1969-1992, (9 folders) (Box 121)
    - Panthertown, Catawba Falls, 1987-1989 (Box 121)
    - Pest control, 1987-1990 (Box 121)
    - Pesticides: Disaster assistance, 1991-1992 (Box 121)
    - Petroleum:
      - 1989-1990 (Box 121)
      - Gas, 1991-1992 (Box 121)
      - Industry, 1992 (Box 121)
      - Marketing, 1989-1992 (Box 121)
      - Oil gauging, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 121)
    - Pigeon River, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 121)
    - Pigeon River, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - Piping Plover, 1991-1992 (Box 122)
    - Pocosin, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 122)
    - Pocosin Lakes National Wildlife Refuge, 1990 (Box 122)
    - Press clippings (Bonner Bridge, Red Wolf), 1988 (Box 122)
    - Price- Anderson Act of 1957, 1987-1988 (Box 122)
    - Public lands
      - 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - Refuges, 1991 (Box 122)
    - Public Utility Holding Company Act (PUHCA), 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - Radon, 1992 (Box 122)
    - RCRA (Resource Conservation Recovery Act):
      - Chemical waste, 1991-1992 (Box 122)
      - Price, 1992 (Box 122)
      - Solid waste, 1992 (Box 122)
    - Red Tide, 1987-1988 (Box 122)
    - Renewable Energy Technology, 1987-1990 (Box 122)
    - RGC Minerals, Inc. mining: Halifax Co., 1991 (Box 122)
    - Rivers, 1989 (Box 122)
    - Rural development
      - 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - North Carolina, 1988-1990 (Box 122)
    - Rural Electrification Administration, 1986-1989 (Box 122)
    - Shearon-Harriss Nuclear Power Plant:
      - 1986-1987 (Box 122)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 122)
    - Shelton Laurel, 1991 (Box 122)
    - Smokies: (Box 123)
      - 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Air, 1992 (Box 123)
      - Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 123)
      - General, 1991 (Box 123)
      - Hearings and statements, 1987-1990 (Box 123)
      - Legislation, 1987-1989 (Box 123)
      - Swain County:
        - Correspondence and bill drafts, 1967-1989 (Box 123)
        - Economics and history, 1958-1988 (Box 123)
      - Wilderness background, 1965-1987 (Box 123)
    - Soil conservation, 1987-1990 (Box 123)
    - Solid waste:
      - 1989 (Box 123)
      - Recycle, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Solid Waste Management, 1988-1989 (Box 123)
    - Superfund, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Sustainable agriculture, 1988 (Box 123)
    - Swain County, 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 123)
    - Swain County: (Box 124)
      - 1987-1992, (4 folders) (Box 124)
      - Amendment, 1991 (Box 124)
      - Briefing papers, 1943:Fontana Agreement, 1943-1991 (Box 124)
      - Lake levels, 1991 (Box 124)
      - North Shore cemeteries, 1986-1990 (Box 124)
    - Thermal KEM, 1991 (Box 124)
    - Timber East, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Timber industry/Wildlife conservation, 1991-1992 (Box 124)
    - Timber management, 1992 (Box 124)
    - Tobacco, 1989 (Box 124)
    - Tongass National Forest Reform, 1989-1990 (Box 124)
    - Toxic waste, 1990-1992 (Box 124)
    - Tropical Forests: Organization for tropical studies, 1987-1990 (Box 124)
    - TVA:
      - 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 124)
      - Lake levels, 1991-1992 (Box 124)
    - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development, 1992 (Box 124)
    - Waste, 1988-1990 (Box 124)
    - Waste incinerator, 1990 (Box 124)
    - Waste minimization, 1987-1990 (Box 124)
    - Waterworks, 1991 (Box 125)
    - Western North Carolina:
      - Mountains, 1991 (Box 125)